export const quizdata = [
    {
    question: "Which of the following is used in React.js to increase performance?",
    options: ["Virtual DOM", "Original DOM", "Both A and B", "None of the above"],
    answer: 1
   },
   {
    question: "What is ReactJS?",
    options: ["Server-side framework", "user interface framework", "both A and B", "None of the above"],
    answer: 2
   },
   {
    question: "Identify the one which is used to pass data to components from outside",
    options: ["Render with arguments", "setState", "PropTypes", "props"],
    answer: 4
   },
   {
    question: "Who created React.js?",
    options: ["Jordan Mike", "Jordan Walke", "Time Lee", "Jordan Lee"],
    answer: 2
   },
   {
    question: "In which language is React.js written?",
    options: ["Python", "JavaScript", "Java", "PHP"],
    answer: 2
   },
   {
    question: "What is Babel?",
    options: ["JavaScript compiler", "JavaScript interpreter", "JavaScript transpiler", "None of the above"],
    answer: 1
   },
   {
    question: "Which of the following port is the default where webpack-dev-server runs?",
    options: ["3000", "3306", "3030", "8080"],
    answer: 4
   },
   {
    question: "How many elements can a valid react component return?",
    options: ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
    answer: 1
   },
   {
    question: "A state in React.js is also known as?",
    options: ["The internal storage of the component", "External storage of the component", "Permanent storage", "All of the above"],
    answer: 1
   },
   {
    question: "What are arbitrary inputs of components in react also known as?",
    options: ["Elements", "Props", "Keys", "Ref"],
    answer: 2
   },
   {
    question: " In MVC, what does React.js act as?",
    options: ["Model", "Controller", "View", "Middleware"],
    answer: 3
   },
   {
    question: "Identify the smallest building block of React.JS.",
    options: ["Props", "Elements", "Components", "None of the above"],
    answer: 3
   },

];